[
{"question": "How can a Canaanite slave be freed?",
"answer": "A Canaanite slave can be freed by money given by his own agency, provided the money comes from somone else or a document given by the agency of someone else.",
"source": "Kiddushin 1:3"},
{"question": "How can a large animal be acquired?",
"answer": "A large animal is acquired by being handed over to the new owner.",
"source": "Kiddushin 1:4"},
{"question": "How can a small animal be acquired?",
"answer": "A small animal is acquired by being led by the new owner.",
"source": "Kiddushin 1:4"},
{"question": "Can unmarried men be shepherds?",
"answer":"Yes, unmarried men can be shepherds",
"source":"Kiddushin 4:14"},
{"question": "Can two unmarried men sleep under one cloak?",
"answer":"Yes, two unmarried men may sleep under one cloak",
"source":"Kiddushin 4:14"},

{"question":"What is the status of a child born to a man who remarried his divorced wife after she had also been remarried, his chalutzah, or a close relative of his chalutzah?", 
"answer":"The child is not a mamzer. This act is punishable by malkut.", 
"source":"Yevamot 4:12"},   
{"question":"What is the status of a child born to a man who married the close relative of his divorced wife?", 
"answer":"The child is a mamzer. This act is punishable by karet.", 
"source":"Yevamot 4:12"},   

{"question":"What is the effect of a get given to a yavamah after another has been given to her co-wife?", 
"answer":"It has an effect. The first yibum bond was not entirely severed.", 
"source":"Yevamot 5:1"},
{"question":"What is the effect of a maamar done with a yavamah after another has been performed with her co-wife?", 
"answer":"It has an effect. The first yibum bond was not entirely severed.", 
"source":"Yevamot 5:1"},
{"question":"What is the effect of a chalitzah done with a yavamah after it has been performed with her co-wife?", 
"answer":"It has an effect. The first yibum bond was not entirely severed.", 
"source":"Yevamot 5:1"},
{"question":"What is the effect of cohabitation done with a yavamah after it has been performed with her co-wife?", 
"answer":"It has no effect at all. It is a forbidden act, but he is permitted to her relatives. Neither a get, maamar, nor chalitzah has an effect after cohabitaion, which erases all other yibum bonds.", 
"source":"Yevamot 5:1"},


{"question": "Is there a difference between a deaf mute minor married off by her father and a woman who became a deaf mute after marriage?",
"answer":"No, in both cases the original biblical marriage can be dissolved by a get.",
"source":"Yevamot 14:2"},
{"question": "Can a woman remarry or perform yibum if she is the only witness claiming that her husband died overseas?",
"answer": "Yes, we believe the woman as a lone witness about her own husband, due to the severe penalities of discovering that her husband is alive.",
"source": "Yevamot 15:1"}

]